plrdatabase.net 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy – PLR Database

## Statement

On this page, you will find all our rules and guidelines about our privacy policy about the PLRdatabase.net platform. This privacy policy sets out how this website uses and protects any information that you give this website when you use this website. This website is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

## Purchasing Information

When you make a purchase here we do not give out any personal information what so ever. Your purchase is safe and secured by a third party company such as PayPal or Clickbank and protected by McAfee and Verisign. PLRdatabase.net will not give out any personal information such as email address, names, credit information or any purchase details.

## Sharing Information

PLRdatabase.net will not give out any personal information such as email address, names or any sign-in information when you enter your details on this site when you are sharing products and posts to other users on this site or off this site. PLRdatabase.net will never sell, share and rent anyone's personal information about you as an individual or any companies.

## Collection of Information

To use and access materials on our site, to register as a member on this site (i.e. login, subscriptions or email subscriptions), or to join our weekly newsletters via our mailing list requires that you provide certain personal information. We use this information in order to contact you to provide you with further information about our services we provide. We will not share your information with any third party or entity.

**We may collect the following information:**

\- Name, username, and password  
\- Contact information including email address

**What we do with the information we gather:**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

\- Internal record keeping.  
\- We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
\- We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
\- From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

## Hyperlinks

This site may contain some hyperlinks to other websites. PLRdatabase.net has no responsibility or control over those other websites. Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

\- whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes  
\- if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [support@plrdatabase.net](mailto:support@plrdatabase.net)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

## Anti-Spam Policy

We hate unsolicited commercial e-mail as much as you do. Also known as Spam or junk e-mail, it is a disservice to the Internet community.

We fully endorse and comply with the requirements of the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act), and all other applicable unsolicited commercial e-mail laws.

If you subscribe to electronic newsletters or other communications from our website, you will always have an option to unsubscribe immediately.  
If you have additional questions, comments or concerns, please contact us by sending an e-mail to the below mailing address and providing us with information relating to your concern.

You may also mail your concerns to us at the following:

or  

This policy was last updated on 05-27-2016

This website may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

Copyright © 2016 MediaCafe Australia, and licensed for use by the owner of this website at [https://www.plrdatabase.net](https://www.plrdatabase.net/). All Rights Reserved. No portion of this document may be copied or used by anyone other than the licensee without the express written permission of the copyright owner.
